<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MY LOVE &#39;GAUTHAMI&#39; A LIFE TIME OF SURPRISES AWAITS YOU on AG</title>
    <link>https://akhilreddy1795.github.io/aglove/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MY LOVE &#39;GAUTHAMI&#39; A LIFE TIME OF SURPRISES AWAITS YOU on AG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://akhilreddy1795.github.io/aglove/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: That Bike Ride</title>
      <link>https://akhilreddy1795.github.io/aglove/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhilreddy1795.github.io/aglove/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Un-Told Story: You remember the night before our return from Pangong Lake, when we were camping under the stars and I was telling everyone my stories? You were enjoying everything while you were by my side. I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel anything special about it that day, but having those moments with you today makes it extremely wonderful.
Next, we went to dinner, and you sat in front of me, while I was listening to music on my JBL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter III: Moments to Remember</title>
      <link>https://akhilreddy1795.github.io/aglove/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhilreddy1795.github.io/aglove/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Mom &amp;amp; Dad Marriage Anniversary: We were travelling back from Srisailam to warangal on our parents&#39; anniversary, we planned to stop for lunch in Hyderabad,As you recall, I invited you to join us for lunch at the same restaurant. Unfortunately, you must travel with your family, and I understand how sad you felt for not being there that day, despite the fact that you made your presence known by surprising me with a cake on my table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II: My First Gift</title>
      <link>https://akhilreddy1795.github.io/aglove/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhilreddy1795.github.io/aglove/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>All my life, I have always been on the giving side, never been on the receiving end. For the first time in my life, I received a present from someone other than my family and it was from you. That day, I just wanted to give you everything I had. I never had that feeling before, and it made me feel so glad about how much I meant to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: Our First Date</title>
      <link>https://akhilreddy1795.github.io/aglove/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhilreddy1795.github.io/aglove/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>I had no idea how this date thing works, and with the image I carry, there was no way for me to contact any friends, then Google came to my rescue. since I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to go empty-handed, I quickly went and collected the bunch of roses and already had my Amazon purchase delivered the previous night, all I need is to start my journey at 4 in the morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://akhilreddy1795.github.io/aglove/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhilreddy1795.github.io/aglove/contact/</guid>
      <description>Future Plans  We must take that road trip to London in our lifetime; it has always been my dream.  Build our crazy farm house with you and I&amp;rsquo;ll start living my golden years alongside you.  Build a watchtower in the farm home for stargazing at night.  On our property, we are going to build a tree house.  I need a water ski boat to ride on my village&amp;rsquo;s lake.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
